[{"answer": "I know it because I know the market pretty well.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Do we know that for a fact?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "I guess maybe they've gotten into it for a while in -- they sort of begin in Iowa, then they go to New Hampshire, it's a little bit restrained there, and they get to South Carolina.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "That may be overstated a little.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Armageddon really?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I'm not moving at any direction at all.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Are you moving towards Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "You can -- you can emphasize and sympathize with Newt.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Can this make a difference in the way that Mitt Romney's super PACs really hammered Newt Gingrich's popularity?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "It was -- some of it was unfair.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Or was it all fair in love and electoral war?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "He wins all four, he's there, right?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "I would say, and then practically --", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "You would assume so?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Gingrich or Santorum.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Is it Gingrich simply on (INAUDIBLE) money?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "I think you go after him on the economy.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "What are his weaknesses?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "He's had success with terrorism, a success and failures with terrorism, but he's had success in the ones that are quite obvious.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Where has he genuinely had success?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Typical.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "What do you make of the furor surrounding it?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Somewhere in between.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Or is it just glorified tittle-tattle?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Well, actually there's been a lot of praise and excitement for the book.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Did you expect it?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Well, I reported on her for about the same way I've been reporting on her for five years in the \"New York Times,\" which is the Obama inner circle really let me in for this book.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "As she says, how do you know what's going on in their head?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Well, because her -- I was -- her aides gave me access.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "How would you know that?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Well, you know, most people who have read the book think it's a pretty flattering portrait of her.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "You must be disappointed, as a \"New York Times\" journalist, that your book is being characterized as a critical attack in many ways on the First Lady, aren't you?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "That is something I think a lot of reporters in Washington don't necessarily understand.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Why are they doing this?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I do think you're on to an excellent question, because the political culture is so nasty and negative that I think there is a good question about if you work really hard on an honest portrayal of these people, that shows their successes and failures and their strengths and their weaknesses, you are at risk of being attacked for that.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Are you slightly sad that the book is being spun, for whatever reason, in this very negative way against the First Lady?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "ORGAN: No, I guess my only point journalistically is that you are relying on other people to tell you how Michelle Obama, in particular, has been feeling throughout this book.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Do we want to live in a world where -- where that doesn't exist?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Well, let me tell you about one scene in the book that I find very poignant.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "I mean you would accept that, right?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Oh, well, you know, I can't take the responsibility for what people are saying on TV shows, when they haven't read the book and they haven't studied this.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "If the First Lady's watching this, and I'm sure it's on her nightly viewing schedule, would you express any regret to her in the way this is all being portrayed?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "You know, first and foremost, you know, that is not anything that we were ever taught to do as soldiers.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "When you saw this video as a soldier first, I guess, what was your reaction to it?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "No, I mean, I don't think that -- again, this isn't appropriate behavior.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Are you surprised that sometimes in the heat of battle soldiers, even the finest Marines, go over the top like this?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "No, I have no idea.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "You think it's more callous than that?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "YNCH: Yeah, I mean, obviously you can look out and tell that, you know, that's not appropriate behavior in any manner.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "And in that kind of video, they ruin everything, don't they?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "It's just incredibly disappointing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Again --", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Should they be kicked out?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I think we should find out from the whole entire case of what the actual back story is --", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "The perpetrators?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "It must be an awful thing for them, isn't it?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Well, I was in a humvee with five other soldiers.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "What was your driving motivation?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "No, no, not at any time was I -- I mean, we had criticism and stuff.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Did you come under a lot of pressure from people in the military, perhaps, and politically as well, not to do that?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "I couldn't find -- I wanted a better life for myself.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Why would a nice young girl from West Virginia join the Army?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "No, never, never.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Did you ever imagine, in your wildest nightmares, that you would one day be on the front line of somewhere like Iraq?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "How is that coming along?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "It does, because I make it mentally.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "I was quite surprised, actually, Is it been getting better for you, slowly but surely?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Just to get kids reading.", "docId": "120112pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "What's the simple idea?", "qSentId": 604}]